

Nikolai Kuzmich Backend developer

Phone: +375 (33) 640-04-64

Email: nikorde@gmail.com

About

I'm Nikolai Kuzmich.

Are you ready to rock □?!

Currently working as a developer at transport company. I'm developing desktop ERP system for cargo transportation. Now I'm looking for a job with a modern technology stack. I love technology and I want professional development and growth. I'm open to new experiences and ready for new challenges!

Age : 32 years old

Languages: Russian, English

Location : Brest, Belarus

Interest : Football, Photoshop, Video editing

Education & Skills



Education

2006-2008
Brest State Technical University
Automation of Technological
Processes and Production

2010-2015 Brest State Technical University Technical operation of vehicles



Experience

2010-2018
YURIDAN LTD
Logistician

2018-2020 YURIDAN LTD Software Developer

Development desktop ERP system. Delphi, PostgreSQL Integration with GPS tracking system and other web services HTML & CSS 40%

JAVASCRIPT 50%

SQL 85%

DELPHI 90%







